Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 9: Miscellaneous, 1701-2011; 56 boxes; 11 items
  - Metal card and carrying case, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Life Membership Pass from Princeton University Athletic Association. Given to Alan D. Wilson.
  - Metal stamp, 1915; 1 box (Box Z.6)
    "Class of 1915"
  - Metal tag, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    from Nassau Hotel, #43.
  - Metal tag, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    with black and orange "P."
  - Metal tag, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    from University Store.
  - Metal trunk., Undated; 1 box (Box Z-Open)
    "Andrew Carnegie Princeton Lake" Black.
  - Mousepad, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2010."
    Class of 2010
  - Mousepad, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2008."
    Class of 2008
  - Mousepad, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
    Circular mousepad. "Welcome Class of 2007."
    Class of 2007
  - Name tag, 1901; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. 1898's 3rd in 1901.
  - Notepad, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    From the Princeton Inn (Forbes)
  - Packet of stickers/patches, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Various tiger pictures. Exxon?
  - Paper mache pumpkin, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    presented to Alger Hiss.
  - Paper Napkins, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Imprinted "The Graduate School Princeton University" with a picture of the south façade of the grad college. Two dinner-size napkins, two cocktail napkins.
  - Paper weight, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    AR.2001.109
    Made for Robert A. Winters in machine shop in Palmer lab. Princeton shield with initials RAW on top.
  - Paperweight(?), 1912; 1 box (Box Z.7)
    glass with gold coin suspended in center, featuring bust of John Grier Hibben on one side, Nassau Hall on other, commemorates Hibben's inauguration.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Princeton Shield with "35." Possibly class of 1935, or another class' 35th reunion.
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2010.123
    Patch with Princeton flag embroidery.
  - Patch, circa 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 2002. Reunion hat and shirt patches.
    Class of 2002
  - Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1930. Princeton shield patch with university motto.
  - Pen, 1982; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Reunions. Class of 1927's 55th.
  - Pen, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    The Pace Center for Community Service pen.
  - Pencil, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
    Orange and black striped pencil with tiger head.
  - Picture, 1956; 1 box (Box Z.6)
    "Princeton" Girl. With collage of seals.
    Gift of Mrs.. George F. Eaton, given 1956.
  - Picture, 1972 June 2; 1 box (Box 21)
    Framed photograph of President Goheen, Mrs. Goheen, President Emeritus Dobbs, Mrs. Dobbs, President-elect Bowen and Mrs. Bowen. At the 50th Reunion of Class of 1922.
  - Picture, Undated; 1 box (Box 21)
    Framed photograph of tiger statue in Palmer Square. "To Zilph Palmer with affectionate regards - Class of 1903."
  - Picture, 1974 March 12; 1 box (Box 22)
    Framed picture and note from Erdham Harris, Class of 1920.
  - Pipe, Undated; 1 box (Box 17)
    AR.2007.004
    White clay pipe
  - Plaque with Princeton shield, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.17)
    AR.2003.004
  - Plastic Cicada clip, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
  - Plastic Princeton Shield, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.17)
    hung from a "With One Accord" ribbon.
  - Plastic tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    AR.2002.079
    with a P on it.
  - Pocket knife, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    silver, Princeton Club of New York engraved, with shield.
  - Portrait, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    John Richardson Bayard Rodgers 1775. In a back lit frame.
    Class of 1775
  - Portrait, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Dr. McCosh. Paperweight.
  - Portrait, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
    AR.1995.078
    Wood portrait of President William Bowen.
  - Portrait, 1970 April 28; 1 box (Box 23)
    Wood portrait of President Robert Goheen.
  - Postcard, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    "Princeton" on banners. Framed.
  - Postcard, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    View of Mount Princeton, Colorado.
  - Postcard, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    "Princeton Runabout" Yellow car picture.
  - Postcard, 1980; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    "Wobble-head tigers, Japan" with note on back.
    Sent to Fred Fox '39 from Marianne Consentino '80.
  - Poster, Undated; 1 box (Box B.8)
    "Stop Sucking the Blood of Soweto Princeton OUT of South Africa Vampires Beware" orange on black background
  - Potato chip bag, 2008; 1 box (Box Z.19)
    AR.2008.073
    Image of Nassau Hall; marquee motif "Live from Princeton, it's 78! 30 Rocks!"; in banner "Old Nassau."
    Class of 1978
  - Potato chip bag, 2008; 1 box (Box Z.19)
    Image of Alexander Hall; marquee motif "Live from Princeton, it's 78! 30 Rocks!"; in banner "Old Nassau."
  - Potato chip bag, 2008; 1 box (Box Z.19)
    Image of Blair Hall; marquee motif "Live from Princeton, it's 78! 30 Rocks!"; in banner "Tigertown."
  - Potato chip bag, 2008; 1 box (Box Z.19)
    Image of Lockhart Hall; marquee motif "Live from Princeton, it's 78! 30 Rocks!"; in banner "Tigertown."
  - Pouch, Undated; 1 box (Box B.5)
    Orange scent pouch.
  - Pouch, Undated; 1 box (Box 17)
    Class of 1911. Brown pouch with Princeton Shield and orange and black ribbon with pin attached. Broken pipe and matches inside.
  - P-Rade baton, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.6)
    Reunions. Brown. U seal on metal caps.
  - P-Rade baton, circa 1881-1890; 1 box (Box Z.6)
    Reunions. Black with "Princeton college" ribbon.
  - Princeton Bookmark, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Gift to Robert A. Winters. '35 and RAW inscribed on front.
  - Princeton Gate Model, Undated; 1 box (Box Mudd foyer)
    Nickel(?)-plated scale model of Fitz Randolph Gate, created by A. Duna and Co. of Hoboken, NJ.
    AR.1999.031
    Presented by C. G. Meeks, Jr., member of the Princeton class of 1931.
  - Princeton Megaphone, undated; 1 box (Box Z-Open (under stairs))
    Black megaphone with orange trim around the ends and a large orange "P" on the top.
    AR.2013.113
    Gift of Robert L. Kress '49
  - Princeton Outing Club Patch, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Princeton Shield with "P.O.C."
  - Princeton Shield sticker, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
  - Princeton sticker, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Black P with orange background.
  - Print, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
    Print for architectural plans. Wooden block. East Pyne?
  - Prints, Undated; 1 box (Box Hallway)
    Original Prints of drawings by John Taylor Arms. 6 prints.
  - Receipt, 1934; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Fine for stealing bell clapper. Mr. TS Winslow '38.
  - Scale model, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.18)
    Graduate School
  - Scissors, 2007; 1 box (Box Z.20)
    AR.2010.121
    Engraved Whitman College dedication scissors; used for ribbon cutting at main dedication event.
  - Sculpture, Undated; 1 item (Item 6)
    Bronze bust of Christian Gauss (1878-1951) by Joe Brown.
  - Seat cushion, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.16)
    Princeton University Stadium
  - Shield, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Shield with gold.
  - Shoulder patch, circa 1951; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    Coat of arms of William of Orange-Nassau; from sleeve of Dutch troops in Korean War.
    EX4910
    Dr. Fred B. Rogers (1947), Friend Temple University Hospital
  - Shreddings, 1952, 1970; 1 box (Box Z.7)
    Shreddings from Posture shots and slides of story with it.
    Class of 1952, 1970
  - Silver platter and case, 1945; 1 box (Box Z.8)
    "Mrs. Harold W. Dodds sponsor of USS Princeton\u2026"
    Gift of Mrs. Harold W. Dodds
  - Silver tag, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Silver tag with inscription "Everything the College Man Needs."
  - Small bust, 1979; 1 box (Box 26)
    of Christian Frederick Gauss, 1878-1951, Dean of the College, 1925-1946. Made by Joel Brown.
    "Minot C. Morgan Jr., '35, b. 1913 d. 1979. Given in Memory by his loving wife Virginia Starr Myers Morgan."
  - Small metal shovel, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    EX4111
    Commemorates Woodrow Wilson's turning of the sod for Seventy-nine Hall, Oct. 20, 1902?
  - Sticker, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Dry adhesive (stamps). Five different ones.
  - Sticker, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Orange paper with Princeton shield and "Princeton University" in black lettering. Adhesive worn off.
  - Temporary tattoo, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.14)
    Class of 1970 reunions.
  - Tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Metal 3". "Princeton"
  - Tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Stuffed animal 6". "Princeton"
  - Tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Stuffed animal 9". "39"
  - Tiger, 1924; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    Plastic 3". From 1924 football game. With button "Princeton."
  - Tiger Claw, circa 1912; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    "Society of the Claw, Princeton University" inscribed on cap.
  - Tiger Claws, circa 1912; 1 box (Box Z.3)
    "Society of the Claw, Princeton University, W.C. Spruance, Jr. no. 82" inscribed on metal cap.
  - Tiger head patch, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    1"x1".
  - Tiger head pillow, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.10)
    "Friends of the Tiger"
  - Tiger sticker for beer cans, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. Class of 1909
  - Tiger sticker for beer cans, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    Reunions. Class of 1919
  - Tile, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    View of Blair Hall 1897. White.
  - Toothbrush, 1939; 1 box (Box Z.2)
    35th reunion.
  - Tote bag, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Tote bag with reunions logo.
  - Toy, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
    Plastic toy with tiger head attached to a trigger which opens and closes mouth.
  - Travel kit, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    White paper with tiger sewing on cover. Contains needles, thread, buttons, bandaids.
  - Umbrella, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    Orange. "92".
  - Umbrella, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.12)
    White. Orange "86".
    Owned by class secretary Henry Jessup '86, given by his niece Miss Mary Frost Jessup.
  - Umbrella, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.11)
    AR.2000.063
    Orange, black and white with Class of 1939 tiger design.
  - Umbrella, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
    Class of 1896 umbrella. Orange and black. "'96"
  - Umbrella, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag 8)
    AR.2010.018
    Off-white umbrella with black and yellow lettering "95." Class of 1895?
  - University seal, 1896; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    EX97
    Original design for Princeton Seal. In frame. "Vitam Mortuis Reddo" and "Dei Sub Numine Viget" on back of drawing.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    orange and black on round metal (?)
  - USS Princeton logos, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Stickers with logo of USS Princeton in envelope
  - USS Princeton pamphlet, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Pamphlet and memorandum describing the USS Princeton
  - Violin and case, circa 1701-1800; 1 box (Box 14)
    Belonged to Karl Langlotz,composer of "Old Nassau". Made Johan Ohberg 18th cent.
    Given by Alexander P Gest, Jr., 1963. Received from Arthur Knapp Jr. '28. Letter enclosed.
  - Wallet, 1980; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    Black leather, "Class of '35 45th Reunion June 1980.
    AR.1996.056.
    Given by Robert A. Winters '35
  - Watercolor, 1909; 1 item
    Gibson girl in orange dress and hat walking tiger on leash. "M.S. Gamble 1909."
  - White tile, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.1)
    with U. seal and motto. "Princeton."
  - Wicker fan, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    with orange ribbon.
  - Wine Bottle (empty) for the 25th Reunion of the Class of 1986, 2011; 1 box (Box 47)
    Label says "The Great Class of 1986, 25th; 25 Years of the Class of 1986"
    Class of 1986
    AR.2012.009
    Gift of Peter Wayner '86.
  - Wooden board, 1909; 1 box (Box C-Open (under stairs))
    "CANE RUSHES." 1903-1909. 2.5'X3'.
  - Wooden sign, 1907; 1 box (Box Z.9)
    "1907"
  - Wooden tiger with bell, 1926; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    "'26"
  - World War II memorial book, 1946; 1 item (Item 1)
    First displayed in Nassau Hall 2/22/46, Washington's Birthday. Commemorates Princetonians who died in service, listed by death date, from 1940-1945. Bronze cover with three crosses as hinges, wood mount. See PAW 3/1/46.
  - Wristband, 2009; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2009.094
    Class of 1969. 40th reunion. Wristband.
  - Unknown, Undated; 1 box (Box Z.4)
    EX4797
    Three bosses given for chess. Belonged to Charles Williams '08.
- Series 10: Pins and Ribbons, 1895-2000; 8 boxes
  This series contains a variety of Princeton-related pins, patches, and ribbons.
  - Class of 1877 pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Princeton seal and motto with "1877".
    Class of 1877.
  - 55th reunion pin, 1933; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "Princeton" and "'78" in black letters; tag "55TH REUNION" inserted.
    Class of 1878.
  - 65th reunion pin, 1952; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "'87" in black; orange ribbon with "65TH REUNION" in black letters.
    Class of 1887.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1915; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Yellow and round with "'90" in black; orange-and-black ribbon with "25TH REUNION" in silver letters.
    Class of 1890.
  - Class of 1892 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "92" in black; orange and black ribbon.
    Class of 1892.
  - 5th reunion pin, 1899; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "94" in black; orange ribbon with "QUINQUENNIAL REUNION JUNE 10, 1899"stitched in black.
    Class of 1894.
  - 18th reunion pin, 1912; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and oval with "18th ANNUAL REUNION" in black; black ribbon with "'94" in golden.
  - Class of 1895 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Black and round with "95" in orange.
    Class of 1895.
  - Class of 1896 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "96" in black.
    Class of 1896.
  - Class of 1896 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Yellow and round with "'96" and "Hello, Old Man, I'm glad to see you back" in black.
  - Class of 1898 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "'98" in black.
    Class of 1898.
  - 3rd reunion pin, 1902; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Yellow and round with "'99" and "Triennial Reunion Princeton, June, 1902" in black.
    Class of 1899.
  - Class of 1901 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1901" in black.
    Class of 1901.
  - Class of 1901 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1901" in black, black rim.
  - 35th reunion pin, 1936; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1901," "35TH REUNION" in black.
  - Miscellaneous pin, circa 1978; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "Halstead 'Jigs' Little," "Princeton 1901," "m. Ruth Archbald November 7, 1914" and "100th Birthday November 7, 1978" in black.
  - 7th reunion pin, 1909; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1902" and "Septennial Reunion June, 1909" in black.
    Class of 1902.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1922; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "'02" and "Twentieth Reunion" in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1927; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "25TH REUNION '02" in black.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1952; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "50th REUNION 1902" in black.
  - Class of 1903 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and black; round with "'03.
    Class of 1903.
  - Class of 1904 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and black; round with "'04".
    Class of 1904.
  - Class of 1905 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and black; round with "'05".
    Class of 1905.
  - Class of 1906 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and black; round with "'06".
    Class of 1906.
  - 3rd reunion pin, 1907; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "04" and "Triennial Reunion" in black.
  - 10th reunion pin, 1914; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1904 Decennial 1914" in black.
  - 60th reunion pin, 1964; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Black and round with "60th Reunion 04" in orange.
  - Class of 1904 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Light Orange and round with "1904" in black.
  - Class of 1904 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and oval with "1904" in black.
  - Class of 1905 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange with "1905" in black.
  - 10th reunion pin, 1915; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1905," "Decennial Reunion" and Princeton University" in black; orange and black fanned ribbon attached.
  - 7th reunion pin, 1914; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "1907 Seventh Annual Reunion" in black, and a camel in the center.
    Class of 1907.
  - Class of 1907 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1907" in black; and a camel drawing overlapped.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1957; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "50th Reunion" and "Princeton 1907" in black, and with "Mac Kerr" in white.
  - Class of 1908 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1908" in black.
    Class of 1908.
  - 45th reunion pin, 1953; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1908, The forty-fifth in 1953" in black; and "Tim Pfeiffer" handwritten in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1934; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "'09" and "Twenty-Fifth Reunion" in black; and with a tiger passing through the numeral zero.
    Class of 1909.
  - 40th reunion pin, 1949; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1909" and "Fortieth Reunion" in black; and "Cameron" handwritten in black.
  - 41st reunion pin, 1950; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1909" and "Forty-first Reunion" in black.
  - 51st reunion pin, 1960; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1909" and "Fifty-first Reunion" in black.
  - Class of 1909 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1909" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - 3rd reunion pin, 1913; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "3rd Reunion" in black.
    Class of 1910.
  - 11th reunion pin, 1921; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "Eleventh Annual Reunion" in black.
  - 20th reunion pin, 1930; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "Twentieth Annual Reunion" in black.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1940; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "Princeton 30th Reunion" in black.
  - 50th reunion pin, 1960; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910," "Princeton" and "50th" in black; and "Brown Rolston" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1910 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1910" and "Princeton" in black; a tag "Jock Emery" inserted.
  - Class of 1913 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Black and round with "13" in orange.
    Class of 1913.
  - 55th reunion pin, 1968; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "1913" and "1968" in black; and "55th Reunion" in orange.
  - Class of 1914 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "'14"in black.
    Class of 1914.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1944; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "Victory Reunion," "1914" and "30th Reunion" in black; Princeton seal and motto.
  - Class of 1915 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1915" and Princeton seal and motto in black.
    Class of 1915.
  - Class of 1920 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1920" and Princeton seal and motto in black.
    Class of 1920.
  - Class of 1921 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "1921's Re-Entry" in orange.
    Class of 1921.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "Princeton" in orange; a modified Princeton seal; and "John Find" handwritten in black.
    Class of 1922.
  - Class of 1921 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "21" and Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1921 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "21"; a photograph of a young man between the numeral, with "'Rod' Brandt" handwritten below.
  - Class of 1921 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "21"; a photograph of a young man between the numerals, with "'Smoke' McWilliams" written below.
  - 15th reunion pin, 1937; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Yellow and round with "Class of 1922," "135" and "Fifteenth Reunion" in black; "Alex Morgan" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "22" in the center, surrounded by twenty-six 2's in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1947; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "22's BIG 25th" in black.
  - 32nd reunion pin, 1954; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1922," "Princeton" and "32nd Reunion" in black.
  - Reunion pin, 1956; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1922," "Princeton" and "1956 Class Dinner" in black.
  - Class of 1922 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1922" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1923 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    White and round with "1923" in black.
    Class of 1923.
  - 23rd reunion pin, 1946; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "23's Twenty-Third," "Joe Fleming" and "'23" in black.
  - Class of 1924 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1924" and the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1951; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "25th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1951" in black; a caricature drawing of Nassau Hall and two tigers in black; "Charlie Millard" handwritten in black.
    Class of 1926.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1956; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "30th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1956" in black; a caricature drawing of a tiger lounging on the beach and smoking; "Margaretta Cook" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1926" and the Princeton seal and motto in black; "GEO. COOK" handwritten in black.
  - 35th reunion pin, 1961; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "35th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1961" in black; a sleeping tiger drawn in black; "GEO. COOK" handwritten in black.
  - 40th reunion pin, 1966; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "40th Reunion," "1926" and "June 1966" in black; a tiger face drawn in black; "Orvel Sebring" handwritten in black.
  - 45th reunion pin, 1971; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "45th" and "'26" in black; a drawing of a tiger lounging on the beach with a Hawaiian dancer dancing; "GEORGE COOK" handwritten in black.
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round "1926" in black.
  - 50th matriculation anniversary pin, 1972; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1922," "1972," "Matriculation Weekend," "Princeton" and "1926" in black; the Princeton seal and motto in black.
  - Class of 1926 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1926" in black; a tiger lounging on the beach drawn in black and green.
  - Class of 1927 Reunion pin, undated; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "1927" in black; the Princeton seal and motto in black; "AL WHITAKER" handwritten in black.
    Class of 1927.
  - 55th reunion pin, 1955; 1 box (Box E.5)
    Orange and round with "55th" and "1929" in black.
    Class of 1929.
  - Reunion pin, 1930; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1930" in orange.
    Class of 1930.
  - 30th reunion pin, 1960; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "30s 30th in 60" in black and orange; a caricature of a tiger on the background.
  - Reunion pin, 1931; 1 box (Box E.6)
    White and round with "Alumni Parade 1931" in orange.
    Class of 1931.
  - 25th reunion pin, 1956; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Black and orange and round "1931" and "25th" in orange.
  - 35th reunion pin, 1966; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Black and orange and round "1931" and "35th" in orange.
  - Reunion pin, 1932; 1 box (Box E.6)
    Green and round with "Alumni Parade 1932" in white.
    Class of 1932.
  - 40th reunion pin, 1972; 1 box (Box E.6)